Finding Aid for The Frick Collection Central Files, 1932-1936 TFC.0400.010
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Central Files, 1935
  - Catalogue, Small - Manuscript, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Contains copy sent to printer of The Frick Collection: Paintings: Summary Catalogue.
  - Catalogue, Small - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Re catalogue specifications, comments on the galley proofs, and costs of The Frick Collection: Paintings: Summary Catalogue.
  - Catalogue, Small - Miscellaneous Bids, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Catalogue, Small, Check Lists, etc. - E. L. Hildreth & Company, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Re printing of small catalogue, check lists of works in The Frick Collection, and postcards. Contains estimates and specs. Painting reproductions done by Meriden Gravure Company. Check lists were for paintings, paintings from Pride's Crossing, sculpture, and enamels.
  - Catalogue Sales Department - Receipts, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Check List - Enamels, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Contains galley proof and typed copy. Printed by E. L. Hildreth & Company.
  - Check List - Paintings, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Check List - Paintings from Pride's Crossing, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Check List - Sculpture, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Contains galley proofs and typed copy. Printed by E. L. Hildreth & Company.
  - Circulation, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Re order in which visitors should move through the rooms of the Collection.
  - Clapp, Frederick Mortimer, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Re Building Congress award for superior craftsmen.
  - Clippings - Frick Art Reference Library, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Oversize news clippings stored in Box A.
  - Clippings - Frick Collection, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Contains letters from clipping services, as well as newspaper clippings. Oversize news clippings stored in Box A.
  - Clippings - Miscellaneous [2 folders], 1935 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
    Primarily contains articles on lawsuit of James Howard Bridge vs. Helen Clay Frick for libel and slander. Photocopies stored in first folder; originals in second. Oversize news clippings stored in Box A.
  - Clocks, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Coat Room Equipment, 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Organization and Policy, 1935 Jan.-Mar. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Includes discussion of selection of marble for Garden Court.
  - Committee on Organization and Policy [3 folders], 1935 Apr.-Dec. (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    Includes discussion of rules and regulations, planting of the Garden Court, hiring of docents, repair of frames by Knoedler, restoration work in the Fragonard Room, and a motion picture screen for Lecture Room. Also contains a copy of a letter from Joseph Duveen to Childs Frick re the lighting of the Boucher Room and the Fragonard Room, and the placement of Romney's Portrait of a Young Lady with a Hat, noting the "beauty and perfection of your marvelous museum." Also includes letters not sent re Helen Clay Frick's rearrangement of the Living Hall, and a letter from Childs Frick complimenting John D. Rockefeller, Jr. on his work on the Collection and the opening.
  - Committee on Organization and Policy - Minutes and Reports of Meetings, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Re labeling of the paintings, opening date (about November 20th tentatively decided upon), the hanging of the West Gallery, furniture in Oval Room, lighting of the paintings, and brick facing to be installed by The Frick Collection on the north wall of Seven East 70th Street (Mrs. Walter B. James' property).
  - Constitution of The Frick Collection, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Construction Account, 1933-1935 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Construction Account - Bills Paid - Miscellaneous, 1933-1935 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Court [Garden Court] - Fountain and Pool, 1933-1935 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Re designs for Garden Court fountain and pool, types and availability of marble to be used, type of fountain, and planting.
  - Court [Garden Court] - Lighting for Plants [2 folders], 1930-1935 (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
    Re sodium vapor lamps for artificial growth. Consulted Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, Inc. Contains research material on artificial lighting related to plant growth. Printed material stored in second folder.
  - Court [Garden Court] - Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Re fret on beams (soffit decoration on Garden Court arcade), and paving of Court.
  - Court [Garden Court] - Models, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Four photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Court [Garden Court] - Photographs and Drawings, 1934-1935 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Ten photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - C - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    Carter, Morris [Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum]
    Cook, Walter W. S.
    Corcoran Gallery of Art
    Courses, Students - Contains application for Student Tickets.
  - Decorating - Gimp, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Contains correspondence from the Hayden Company, and Edward Maag of Bokelmann Trimming Co., Inc.: "Many years ago we made a lot of the gimps, galloons and fringes that were in the Frick Mansion, particularly the Fragonard Gallery. We still have the original documents, designs, and jacquard cards."
  - Decorating - Hanging of Wall Fabrics, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Contains correspondence with The Hayden Company.
  - Decorating - Painting and Gilding, 1934-1935 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Work split among three contractors: Frederick Rose & Co. (restoration of Fragonard Room), The Hayden Company, and Angelo Magnanti (gilding).
  - Decorating - Wall Fabrics - Hayden Company, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Contains letter of agreement for West Gallery wall covering and Oval Room, Miscellaneous Paintings Room and Lobby. Includes velvet samples for West Gallery. Also re woodwork for the Oval Room, wall covering in Director's Office, and gimps.
  - Decorating - Wall Fabrics - Johnson & Faulkner, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Contains letter of agreement re wall covering for Lecture Room, Trustees' Room and print room.
  - Decorating - Wall Fabrics - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Re amount of fabric in square yards required and selection of fabrics and colors. Includes May 27, 1935 and May 28, 1935 summaries of conversations/meetings with Helen Clay Frick re decoration of the Collection, the decision not to hire an interior decorator and Childs Frick's wish to do so, inscriptions, marbles, and the color of the borders and base of the Oval Room.
  - Decorating - Wall Fabrics - Mrs. Schmidt [Elena B. Schmidt], 1935 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    Interior decorating consultant.
  - Decorating - Wall Fabrics and Painting and Gilding, 1933-1935 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - D - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Dillon, J. C. Company
    Downs Printing Company
    Dwight, H. G. [Assistant to the Director]
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] [2 folders], 1935 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
    Contains October 30, 1935 letter from Mr. Clapp re his feelings about "the character of the services rendered" by the firm.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor]- Bills re Miss Frick's Account, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Bills re Maintenance Account, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Bills and Requisitions, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Bills for Utilities Chargeable to Construction, 1933-1935 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Bills for Utilities Chargeable to Construction - Memoranda, 1933-1935 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Contracts & Extra Orders, 1935-1936 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Copies of Letters [3 folders], 1935 (Box 23, Folder 11-13)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Costs, Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Estimates, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Memoranda to Job Office, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Minutes of Weekly Conferences, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Statements of Estimated Cost Status, 1935-1936 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractor] - Statements of Expenditures and Commitments, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Elevators, 1933-1935 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Emergencies, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Employees [RESTRICTED FILE], 1935 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Employees - References [RESTRICTED FILE], 1933-1935 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Entrance on 70th Street - Facade, 1934-1935 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Includes mentions of the Frick Art Reference Library lunette, the problem of the Collection's entrance being off-center, and the iron fence at the entrance. Photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Equipment and Materials for Sale, 1934-1935 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Equipment and Supplies - Maintenance, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - E - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Edgell, George H.
    Eisinger, Mr. & Mrs. L. W.
    Exterminating service [Virus Limited, Inc.]
  - Finishes of Switches, Receptacle Plates, Outlets, etc., 1934-1935 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Fire Extinguishers, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fountain on Roof, Library, 1933-1935 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Re planned fountain on Library's penthouse terrace, with statue of St. Francis by Malvina Hoffman.
  - Frick, Childs, Mr., 1935 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Frick, Helen C., Miss, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Contains correspondence and memos summarizing discussions/meetings. Topics covered include the Library terrace garden and fountain, tentative inscriptions for Percy Martin (house employee) and John Holroyd (superintendent), and a proposal for a catalogue vending machine. Also contains discussion among Clapp, Helen Clay Frick and Childs Frick concerning the circulation of visitors throughout the Collection, and the Fricks' desire that the furniture arrangement might remain closer to its original layout. Also contains September 23, 1935 proposal from Duke of Alba to trade two letters signed by Christopher Columbus for Jonghelinck bust in The Frick Collection.
  - Frick Art Reference Library, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Frick Art Reference Library - Bills for Utilities, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Frick Art Reference Library - Dust in Bookstacks, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Frick Art Reference Library - Ethelwyn Manning [Librarian], 1935 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Furniture - Frick Art Reference Library, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Furniture and Furnishings - Office, 1935-1936 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    Contains pencil drawings mounted on board of Collection chairs covered in cotton velvet, and layouts of The Frick Collection Director's Room, Stenographer's Office, Assistant Director's Office, and Secretary's Room.
  - F - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Fifth Avenue Association
    Fire Station
    Foxboro Company
    Freer Gallery of Art
  - Griggs, Maitland F. [Trustee], 1935 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Grounds, 1934-1935 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Contains planting recommendation from Arnold Arboretum at Harvard (Ivan H. Crowell) to Helen Clay Frick.
  - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Guaranty Trust Company of New York - Statements, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Hammond, John Henry [The Frick Collection Counsel], 1935 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    Re tax exemption, the By-laws and Constitution of The Frick Collection, and the effect of the Federal Social Security Act, New York Unemployment laws, and New York Workmen's Compensation Law on the Collection budget.
  - Hardware and Keys - Collection, 1934-1935 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Hardware and Keys - Collection & Library, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Hardware and Keys - Drawings, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Oversize blueprints stored in flat files.
  - Hardware and Keys - Library, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Havemeyer, Horace [Trustee], 1935 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Henry [Lafenetre] [The Frick Collection Engineer], 1935 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Hildreth, E. L. & Co. - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Holmes Electric Protection, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - House Account, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    United States Trust Company of New York.
  - H - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Hale Desk Company Henderson-Baumguard Company, Inc. - Re walnut postcard racks.
    Hines, Mrs. Walker D.
  - Inquiry Sheets Re Progress of Construction Work, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Inscriptions - Drawings and Photographs (Library), 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Oversize items including drawings on tracing paper stored in flat files. Photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Inscriptions - Garnett, Porter, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Designed Library interior and exterior inscriptions. Some oversize drawings on tracing paper stored in Box B.
  - Inscriptions - Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Inscriptions - Pope, John Russell, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Inscriptions to John and Percy, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Re memorial inscriptions to John Holroyd (superintendent) and Percy Martin (house employee) in The Frick Collection Garden Court.
  - Insurance, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Inventory - Furniture and Furnishings - Storage During Construction (Mr. Naughton's Records), 1933-1935 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Invitation to Opening, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Contains correspondence re the invitation list.
  - Invitation to Opening of Collection, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Contains four copies of invitation and an admittance ticket.
  - Juncture of Collection and Library Buildings, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - J - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    James, Mrs. Walter B. - Re letter of agreement re installation of brick facing of her property at Seven East 70th Street.
  - Keys, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - K - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    Kalt Lumber Company
    Kent, H. W. [Metropolitan Museum of Art]
  - Labels - E. L. Hildreth & Co. - Enamels, Sculpture, Boucher and Fragonard Rooms, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    Contains samples of text on placard labels, and discussions of label size, background paper and color. Oversize proof sheets stored in Box B.
  - Labels - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    Re size and shape of labels for the paintings.
  - Labels - Stanley J. Rowland - Paintings, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    Re numbers, size and text of painting labels.
  - Laws - Mr. Hammond's Opinion on N.Y. Unemployment Insurance, Social Security, N.Y. Workmen's Compensation, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Lighting - Caldwell & Company, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Lighting - Caldwell & Company - Eidlitz, Marc & Son, Inc., 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    Includes sample of material for Reading Room lamp shades.
  - Lighting - Caldwell & Company - Memoranda, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Photograph transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopy of photograph.
  - Lighting - Caldwell & Company - Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Oversize pencil drawing on tracing paper stored in flat files.
  - Lighting - Caldwell & Company - Pope, John Russell, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Contains silk samples for lamp shades in the Collection and Library.
  - Lighting - Emergency, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Lighting - Galleries, 1933-1935 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Lighting - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Lunette for Library Building - Joseph A. Coletti, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Lunette was not completed; Coletti released owners from contract: "I regret very much making this decision but I feel that no matter what changes might be made in the Pontormo design, under present conditions there would always be opposition. Besides this difficulty there are too many people to please, which in itself, is an impossible situation."
  - Lunette for Library Building - Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Frederick Mortimer Clapp to Helen Clay Frick "I am reluctantly forced to admit that my suggestion for the lunette is a failure, detracting rather than adding to the severity and style of the building."
  - Lunette for Library Building - Office of John Russell Pope, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Lunette for Library Building - Photographs, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - L - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Ledyard, Isabel
    Lee, Albert R., & Co. Inc.
    Life Insurance - Aetna Life Insurance Company.
    Lindsay, Miss
    Luks, Estate of George B.
  - Mailing List, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Does not contain mailing list, just a few requests for names to be added.
  - Maintenance of Equipment, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Maintenance of Equipment - Permits, Licenses, etc., 1933-1935 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Marble, 1932-1935 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Measurements re Buildings, 1933-1935 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Includes square/cubic footage of the Collection and Library, by floor.
  - Mellon, Andrew W. [Trustee], 1935 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Memoranda - F. M. Clapp and I. D. Matthew [Clerk of the Works], 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Memoranda - F. M. Clapp and W. J. Naughton [Custodian], 1935 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    Includes mentions of the disposition of Liveries with crested buttons used during Mr. Frick's time, and cleaning of Boucher panels.
  - Memoranda - Rough Notes on Weekly Conferences, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Memoranda on Plans [3 folders], 1935 Jan.-Sep. (Box 26, Folder 21-23)
  - Memoranda on Plans, 1935 Oct.-Dec. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda on Plans - Mr. Clapp's Notes [4 folders], 1935 (Box 27, Folder 2-5)
    Includes summaries of conversations and meetings with Helen Clay Frick and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Memoranda on Plans - Mr. Dwight [Assistant to the Organizing Director], 1935 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda on Plans - Mr. Matthew's Notes, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Re gallery lighting, special light for stimulating plant growth in the Court, motion picture projectors, air conditioning, and a summary of proposed picture light reflectors, room by room.
  - Memoranda on Plans - Mr. Watson [Superintendent], 1935 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Contains reports on visits to the Brooklyn Museum, the Freer Gallery, the Corcoran Gallery, the National Gallery, the Worcester Museum, the Fogg Art Museum, and the Boston Museum of Fine Arts re their procedures and staffing. Also contains a September 9, 1935 seven-page memo to Clapp listing work still to be done in The Frick Collection.
  - Models - Photographs, etc., 1934-1935 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Re models for Collection and Library exterior stone work, exterior woodwork, interior stone, woodwork and bronze models. Modelers for exterior work: Ricci & Zari. Modelers for interior work: Charles G. Peters. Thirty-six photographs of models transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs.
  - Morgan, Junius S. [Trustee], 1935 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Museum Management, 1932-1935 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - M - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Masterson, Harriet H.
    Metropolitan Refining Co. Inc. - Re vaporene treatments for air conditioning system, analyses of water in cooling tower and air washer circuit.
    Morison, C. T. & Company, Inc. - Re electrical supplies and appliances.
  - New York Telephone Company, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - N - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    New York Building Congress - Group photograph of workers/architect/builders holding Craftsmanship Awards, May 2, 1935 transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopy of photograph.
    New York Edison Company, Inc.
  - Office Supplies, 1933-1935 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Offices - Plans, Equipment, 1934-1935 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Primarily contains vendor brochures on desks, chairs, adding machines (including Comptometer), and filing cabinets.
  - Opening - Announcements, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Contains sample of announcements and some mailing lists.
  - Opening - Invitations, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    Contains samples of the invitation, and lists of invitees.
  - Opening - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Re arrangements with New York Police Department and private detective T.J. Tunney, and chair rental. Includes November 25, 1935 letter to Police Department requesting permission to obtain four tear-gas guns.
  - Opening - Publicity, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Contains drafts of December 11, 1935 press releases. In addition to information about the opening, the press releases includes information on Henry Clay Frick's will, the Board of Trustees, the process of turning the residence into a museum, admission policies, the order in which rooms will be visited and the works in each, invitees to the opening, and a biographical sketch of Frederick Mortimer Clapp.
  - Opening - Publicity - Complete Set Given to Newspapers [3 folders], 1935 (Box 28, Folder 3-5)
    Contains press releases, a floor plan and photographs of works of art (11) and rooms in The Frick Collection (12). Some sets are incomplete. Oversize floor plans stored in Box C. Photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Opening - Publicity - Lee & Ross [Ivy Lee & T.J. Ross.], 1935 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Re press placements.
  - Opening - Publicity - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Re special press viewings for press, requests for photographs to publish, and Collection thank you letters to press for the coverage.
  - Opening of the Library, 1934-1935 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Contains brief list of arrangements to make, Mr. Clapp's list of invitees, and correspondence related to press coverage.
  - Organ, 1933-1935 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    See also Aeolian-Skinner Organ Company. Re cleaning and tuning; adding stops and changing console; adding new, four manual, supplementary console; and installing sound transmission apparatus.
  - Organ Sound Transmission, 1933-1935 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Contains correspondence with Bludworth, Inc. re transmission of organ music from hall to Garden Court. See also Bludworth, Inc.
  - O - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Otis Elevator Company
  - Painting - Plain, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Contains schedule of paint colors for The Frick Collection. Subcontractor Joseph A. Reid, Inc.
  - Passes Issued for Entry to Building, 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Pay Rolls and Reports of Overtime [RESTRICTED FILE], 1935 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Personnel [RESTRICTED FILE], 1935 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Departments, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Photographers, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Contains lists of photographs. Photographs of Collection interiors and art collection transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs.
  - Pipe Lines, 1934-1935 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Picture Outlets, 1934-1935 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Re electrical outlets for gallery lights.
  - Planting - Committee on Organization and Policy, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Re Garden Court planting. November 20, 1935 copy letter from Rockefeller to Frederick Law Olmsted expresses his displeasure with the planting, most of which was not thriving.
  - Planting - Findlay, Hugh [landscape architect], 1935 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Planting - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 9)